2048年
The year is 2048.
技术发展不再循规蹈矩
Evolving technologies can no longer be regulated.
危险的技术进步让犯罪形态从此改变
Dangerous advancements forever alter the criminal landscape.
警察未做好准备
Police are not prepared.
执法机关建立新的防线
Law enforcement combats this corruption
与这些罪恶斗争
with a new line of defense...
但他们生来并不平等
But not all are created equal.
DRN系列的理念是尽可能与人类一样
The idea behind the DRNs was to be as human as possible.
他们基于一个叫合成灵魂的开发程序
They were based on a program called synthetic soul.
那是个疯狂机器人吧
That's one of the crazy ones.
-我打头阵  -行动
- I'll lead you in? - Let's go.
如今所有警察  包括人类和机器人
Now all cops-- human and manmade together--
共同投入战斗  保卫我们
take on the battle to watch over us all.
机器之心
第一季  第二集
你太棒了
You are incredible.
我们来点更舒服的  好吗
Let's get more comfortable, hmm?
可以吗
That okay?
你紧张吗
You nervous?
看起来你脑袋里想的很多啊
It seems like you've got a lot on your mind.
实际上  是的
Actually... I do.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我通过所有的测试了  我是干净的
I've passed all my tests. I'm clean.
你介意吗
Would you mind?
不会疼的
This won't hurt.
你不想做的事可以不做
You don't have to do anything if you don't want to.
人们找我有各种各样的理由
People come to me for all sorts of reasons.
有人想聊聊  有的则只想抱一抱
Some want to talk or just to be held.
咱们干嘛不找点乐子呢
Look, why don't we just have some fun?
人们用不同的方式来寻求交流
People look for connections in different ways.
寻找关心他们的人
Someone who cares about them.
安德烈
Andrei!
看这个
最后一项
Last one.
我保证
I promise.
驾照
姓名  塞巴斯蒂安·琼斯
穿上衣服
Get dressed.
楼上犯罪现场调查员弄完了吗
CSI finished upstairs?
不会太久的  长官
Shouldn't be long, sir.
你是个机器人
You're a bot.
对  我是
Yes, I am.
太帅了  你能做什么
Cool! What can you do?
帅爆了
Whoa. Oh, awesome!
你也是个机器人吗
Are you a robot, too?
不  我是人类
No, I'm human.
那你能做什么
Oh. What can you do?
看着
Watch this.
不不不
No, no, no.
不疼的  我有...我这是合成肢
It doesn't hurt. I got... I got a synthetic leg!
我没当过孩子都知道那很恐怖
I haven't even been a child, and I know that would scare one.
你怎么回事
What's the matter with you?
你满满的负能量  老兄
You have negative energy, man.
我的能量很正
My energy's great.
那为什么你不喜欢孩子
Why don't you like kids?
我从未说过我不喜欢孩子
I never said I don't like kids.
是你说我不喜欢的
You said I don't like kids.
孩子能感觉到磁场的  约翰
Children can sense electromagnetic fields, John.
胡话连篇
That's a bunch of baloney.
他们也能感觉到不舒服  沮丧
They can sense discomfort, frustration
还有负能量
and bad energy.
和猫科动物一样
As do felines.
我猜你也不喜欢猫  对吗
I bet you have an issue with cats, too, am I right?
我和猫的问题不关你事
Hey. My issue with cats is none of your business.
我对猫过敏
I'm allergic to cats.
也许猫也对你过敏
Maybe the cats are allergic to you.
你从没想过这个吗
You ever consider that?
受害者名叫塞巴斯蒂安·琼斯
Victim is ID'd as Sebastian Jones.
用现金付的房费
He paid for the room with cash.
前台说他是跟一个女人一起来的
Front desk said he showed up
红头发  二十来岁的样子
with a woman. Red hair, 20s.
约半小时后  两个男人出现
About a half hour later, two men showed up.
现场没有指纹
There are no fingerprints.
依我看从法医那里得不到任何信息
I don't think we're gonna get anything from forensics.
这里的一切都被污染了
Everything is tainted in here.
他们使用了DNA炸弹
They used a DNA bomb.
我讨厌那玩意
I hate that stuff.
第三代吸音环
Absorption round, third gen.
不会发出任何声音  这帮人很厉害
Wouldn't have made a sound. These guys are good.
有监控录像吗
Any surveillance?
她下午六点一刻进来的
She came in at 6:15 p.m.
他们二十分钟之后就到了
They arrived 20 minutes later.
他们戴着闪光面具
They're wearing flashmask.
他们带走了他的包
They took his bag.
约翰
John.
她是个机器人
She's an android.
关于受害者我们都知道些什么
What do we have on our victim?
塞巴斯蒂安·琼斯是一个高端性爱机器人制造商
Sebastian Jones was a high-end sex trade bot-maker.
真可惜他死了
Yeah, too bad he's dead.
要不还能帮你造个女朋友
Could've made you a girlfriend.
注册网恋资料的人又不是我
I'm not the one with the online dating profile.
我可没有注册什么网恋资料
I don't have an online dating profile.
现在有了
You do now.
摩羯座
"Capricorn
喜欢冒险
who loves danger."
好吧  既然你正在写  干嘛不顺便写上
Okay. While you're at it, why don't you put down
"最近在高速公路事故中失去了搭档"
"recently lost partner in tragic freeway accident."
我们现在都有哪些线索
Guys, what do we have?
塞巴斯蒂安·琼斯的公司
Sebastian Jones' company
叫奥瑞立安智人公司
is called Orillian Sapients.
他们主要制造高端性爱机器人
They specialize in advanced sexual robotics.
这个是他的性爱机器人吗
Is this one of his sexbots?
目前还不知道
We don't know.
性爱机器人都是注册过的
Sexbots are licensed.
这个在谁的名下
Who's it registered to?
不在任何人的名下
It's not registered to anybody.
它肯定有主
Someone owns it.
肯定注册过
It has to be registered.
关于他我们还知道些什么
What else do we know about his life?
没有配偶  没有孩子
No spouse, no kids,
没有犯罪记录
no criminal record.
是个守法的商人
Legitimate businessman.
-发明家  -他名下有23项专利
- Inventor. - He has 23 patents
被誉为人工脸红反应领域的
to his name and is credited as a pioneer in developing
研发先驱
the artificial blush response.
这座城市里所有的热血男儿
Every red-blooded man in this city
都受过这位陨落天才的好处
owes a debt to this fallen genius.
为什么  就因为他制造性爱机器人吗
Why, because he makes sex trade bots?
叫他们"约炮机器人"就行
Call 'em "Bang bots."
其实他们喜欢这个名字
They actually like it.
你这是经验之谈吗
And you know this from experience?
你这话说的好像这是坏事
You say it like it's a bad thing.
自从性爱机器人问世
Crimes in the sex trade are down
-性交易中的犯罪下降了38%  -是吧
- 38% since the bots were introduced. - Right?
-多划算  -跟你上床的
- Do that math. - The fewer real women
真正的女人越少  理查德
that have to sleep with you, Richard,
这个世界就越美好
the better off the world is. Okay.
关于他我们还知道什么
What else do we know about him?
塞巴斯蒂安·琼斯无力支付账单
Sebastian Jones couldn't pay his bills.
三个月前奥瑞立安智人公司宣布破产
Orillian Sapients declared bankruptcy three months ago.
债权人拿走了他的所有资产
Creditors seized all of his assets,
现在都被收放在一个寄存仓库里
and now they're currently sitting in a repo storage facility.
被告人  塞巴斯蒂安·琼斯
找到了一张法院传票
Found a court summons.
塞巴斯蒂安受到了起诉
Sebastian was being sued.
我是肯尼思
Kennex.
你的案子有点不对劲
Your case just got weird.
我刚刚给你发了点东西  收到了吗
I just sent you something. You get it?
收到了
Yeah, I got it.
犯罪现场调查员检查了宾馆的那部电梯
The CSIs went through the elevator at the hotel,
扫描了这些男人可能接触的地方
Scanning spots these guys
想要提取他们的DNA
Likely touched, trying to pick up some DNA on them.
在这些男人身上没能找到DNA
Yeah. We didn't find any DNA on the guys,
但是我们发现了别的东西
but we found something else.
在那里他们检测到第一个样本
That's the first sample they pulled.
她所触及之处  留下的都是一个
Everywhere she touched, there was DNA from a 25-year-old girl
叫妮可·奎斯特的25岁女孩的DNA
Named Nicole Bloomquist,
她三周前在停车场被绑架了
who was abducted three weeks ago from a parking garage.
你是说我们找的这个性爱机器人
Are you telling me the sexbot we're looking for
留下的DNA都是那个姑娘的吗
is leaving this girl's DNA?
貌似是这样的
It seems that way.
怎么会
How?
对呀  怎么回事
Correct. How?
坐好咯
Ah, there you go.
很好  很好
Perfect, perfect.
你这个扭来扭去的小讨厌
Oh, look at you. Wriggle monster.
来
Okay.
妈妈要把它拿走啦
Mommy'll take it then.
把手给我
Give me your hands,
把脸也擦擦
give me your face.
真漂亮
Beautiful.
又发生了一起绑架案
Another abduction happened.
和妮可·奎斯特案一样的作案模式
Same M.O. as Nicole Bloomquist.
20多岁女性  停车楼
20-something female, parking structure.
摄像机瘫痪
Cameras were disabled.
所以没有绑架案的监控录像
There's no surveillance of the abduction.
而且我又发现了三起新案件
And I found three more missing persons cases
遵循相同的模式
with the same pattern.
也就是说他们先对摄像机下手  再抓人
So, they kill the cams and then take the women.
没错  不过这一次他们落了东西
Yeah, except this time, something was left behind.
他当时在车里  他叫维克多
He was in the car. His name is Victor.
我能跟他谈谈吗
Can I talk to him?
也许应该由我来谈
Maybe I should talk to him.
他不擅长跟孩子交流
He's not good with kids.
-还有猫  -那不是...
-Or cats. - That-that's not...
我可会哄孩子了  真的
I'm great with kids, really.
我是肯尼思警探
I'm Detective Kennex.
你一定就是维克多了  是吧
You must be, uh, Victor, right?
维克多可真是个好名字
Victor's a-a good name.
是一个优秀  坚强的名字
It's a good, strong name.
我知道这很难
Look, I know this must be hard...
但是你一定要勇敢一点  好吗
But I need you to be brave. Okay?
我需要你告诉我你妈妈遭遇了什么事
I really need you to tell me what happened with your mom.
你喜欢他吗
You like him?
如果你想要  我可以把他给你
I'll give him to you if you want him.
但是你得保证
But you got to promise me
要好好照顾他
to look after him
因为他对我来说很重要
because he means a lot to me.
-我保证  -保证吗
- I promise. - You promise?
好吧
Okay.
我相信你
I trust you.
听着  维克多
Look, Victor.
我真的很需要你的帮助
But I really need your help.
需要你告诉我你妈妈遭遇了什么
Need you to tell me what happened with your mom.
你们当时是在一辆车里  是吗
You guys were in a car, right?
你妈妈走下了车
Your mom got out.
她去扔垃圾了
She went to put the trash away.
然后发生了什么
Then what happened?
我看到了一辆车
I saw the car.
你看到里面有什么人了吗
Did you see who was in it?
有两个男人
Two men.
两个男人
Two men?
之后发生了什么呢
What happened then?
那辆车开走了
The car drove away.
是什么样的车  什么颜色的
What kind of car was it? What color?
是一辆大大的银色的车
It was a big, silver car.
一辆大大的银色的车
A big, silver car.
很好
That's good.
我妈妈什么时候来
When is my mom coming?
维克多
Hey, Victor.
你做的很好
You did really good.
怎么了
What's up?
通过离那个停车场一个街区的交通摄像头
CSI found the silver sedan
犯罪现场调查员找到了那辆银色轿车
on a traffic cam a block from the parking structure.
但是追踪牌照查到的却是一辆红色SUV
The license plates tracked back to a red SUV.
他们在用偷来的车牌
They're using stolen plates.
我们找了城里的每一个车牌扫描器
We got every plate scanner in the city
去寻找那些标签
looking for those tags.
我们会找到那辆车的
We'll find that car.
两个女孩儿被人用相同的手法劫持
Okay, two girls were abducted with the same M.O.
其中的一个女孩
And one of them,
她的DNA出现在了一个性爱机器人身上
her DNA was found on the sexbot
那个机器人在塞巴斯蒂安·琼斯被谋杀时
who was with Sebastian Jones
和他在一起
when he was murdered.
我觉得我们得集中注意力
I think we should focus on
去找那个和塞巴斯蒂安在一起的性爱机器人
finding the sexbot that was with Sebastian.
假如我们可以取得她的记忆
If we can access her memory,
我们说不定就可以看见
we might be able to see
那晚酒店里发生了什么
what happened in the hotel that night.
并且确定凶手身份
And identify who did it.
这是我们找到那些失踪女人的最好机会
That's our best bet for finding the missing women.
各位  我貌似有了一个新角度了
Guys, I might have a new angle.
我彻查了被你们传唤的那些人
I dug into those summonses you found.
塞巴斯蒂安的前生意伙伴洛伦佐·肖
Sebastian's former business partner Lorenzo Shaw
告他侵犯知识产权
was suing him for intellectual property infringement
机器人制造商和前生意伙伴闹僵
两人开始打官司
并且刚刚在市中心为自己
and he just opened a sexbot showroom downtown
性爱机器人发展新路线公布
开了家性爱机器人展览厅  这就是动机
for himself-- it's motive.
他可能卷入了这件事
He could be involved.
查清他的底细
Check him out.
你和那个小孩相处得真是惊人的好  约翰
You were surprisingly good with that kid back there, John.
即使你得用个长颈鹿贿赂他
Even though you had to bribe him with a giraffe.
谢谢
Thanks.
你觉得他的妈妈有可能还活着吗
Do you think his mother is still alive?
我希望如此
I hope so.
她多消失一个小时
Every hour she's gone
就意味着她活着被我们找到的机会少了一分
diminishes the chance of us finding her alive.
当某人死了的时候你怎么跟一个小孩说呢
What do you tell a small child when someone dies?
我从没想过这个
I've never considered that.
你会怎么跟一个小孩说呢
What you would tell a small child.
你和一个成年人怎么说就和小孩怎么说
Well, you say the same thing that you'd say to an adult.
他们会怎么说
What do they say?
你告诉他们死了的人去了一个更好的地方
You tell them that the person that died has gone to a better place.
为什么大家会这么说
Why would anyone say that
既然没有办法真的知道
when there's no way to really know
人死了之后究竟会去哪
where living things go when they stop living?
这么说可以给人希望和慰藉
It's designed to give hope and comfort.
减轻伤痛
To ease the pain.
人们相信这个因为他们需要相信
People believe it because they need to.
我研究的数据表明
Hmm, the data I've studied suggests
一个人存在过的最好证明
that the best proof of one's existence
就是在他们死后还有人记得他们
is if one is remembered after they're gone.
你搭档的儿子也是这样吗
Was your partner's son told
被告知他的父亲去了更好的地方
that his father went to a better place?
不知道
I don't know.
你没跟搭档的儿子说过话
You never spoke to your partner's son?
我能理解这对你来说很艰难
I can understand why that would be hard for you.
你们把我儿子怎么了
What did you do with my son?
别担心
Don't worry.
他应该已经在警方那儿了
The authorities will have him by now.
-你看  我们不是恶人  -我有钱
- You see, we're... we're not monsters. - I have money!
你要什么我都给你
Anything you want, anything.
什么都行
I'll give you anything.
求你了  我只想见到我儿子
Please, I just want to see my son...
我已经得到想要的东西了
I already have what I want.
不  不  不要
No, no, no!
你的前任合伙人  塞巴斯蒂安·琼斯
Your ex-partner, Sebastian Jones,
你最后一次见他是什么时候
when was the last time you saw him?
六  七个月前
Six months? Seven?
我们最近有点闹不和
We'd been sort of on the outs lately.
闹不和
"On the outs"?
你都起诉他了
You were suing him.
我拥有我们在奥瑞立安
I have intellectual property rights
共同创作的产品的知识产权
on designs we developed together at Orillian.
塞巴斯蒂安裸了之后知识产权会怎么处理
What happens to the I.P. rights now that Sebastian's naked?
我是说  他死了之后
Um, I mean "Dead."
现在塞巴斯蒂安已经死了
Now that Sebastian's dead.
知识产权会怎么处理
What happens to the I.P. rights?
他们当然会转回我的名下
Well, they would naturally revert to me.
这个是你的模特吗
Is this one of your models?
她不是
No, she's not mine.
这个呢
What about this one?
还有这个
Or this one?
你见过这些女人吗
You ever seen these women before?
没见过  但她们不是合成人
No, but they're not synthetics.
-你怎么能确定  -干我这行
- How can you be sure? - In my line of work,
自会知道
you get to know.
我很久没见过你这种型号了
You know, I haven't seen one of you in a while.
新型性爱机器人上还有点你身上的老技术呢
The latest sexbots have a little bit of your old tech in them.
她们可以与雇主建立情感交流
They're capable of bonding empathetically with their clients.
感知他们的情绪
Sense their moods...
并作出回应
and respond accordingly.
这可是个了不起的成就
It's a significant achievement.
要是你的机器人如此与众不同
If your bots are so special,
塞巴斯蒂安怎么会欠一屁股债
why was Sebastian so in debt?
要是你了解塞巴斯蒂安  你就会明白了
Well, if you knew Sebastian, you'd understand.
他是个艺术家
He was an artist.
我们发了大财
We were making good money.
但他却下定决心要研发新的生产线
But he was determined to create the next line.
要青出于蓝胜于蓝
Better than the last.
他把我们所有的资金都投入到了
He sunk all our capital into
新的生产车间  加工工具和零部件上了
new fabs, tooling, subsystems.
他把整个公司都押上了
He bet the whole company on it.
然后我们最大的客户终止了合约
And then our biggest client cancelled their contract with us.
让我们大吃一惊
Took us completely by surprise.
让我们破产了
Bankrupted us.
你们最大的客户是谁
Who was your biggest client?
如果你不想说也行
Ah, if you don't want to tell me, that's okay.
我们只要勒令你交出销售记录
We'll just subpoena your records.
在我们检查期间让你停业几天
Shut you down for a few days while we go through them.
是一个阿尔巴尼亚财团
It was an Albanian consortium.
他们说正在取缔中间商
They said they were cutting out the middle man.
你是说他们找到了新的货源
You mean they found a new supplier?
似乎是
Apparently.
塞巴斯蒂安不相信会有人制造得出
Sebastian couldn't believe that anyone could build
比我们的更好的性爱机器人
a better sexbot than us.
我给你看的第一张照片
The first picture I showed you.
她属于那些阿尔巴尼亚人吗
Did she belong to the Albanians?
塞巴斯蒂安被杀当晚去酒店是因为她吗
Is she why Sebastian was at the hotel the night he was killed?
我不知道
I wouldn't know.
听着  我不想再谈论这件事了
Look, I-I don't want to talk about this anymore.
他们威胁你了吗
Did they threaten you?
没有
No...
他们是很好的客户  他们总是及时付款
They were good clients. They always paid on time.
关于他们  我就只能透露这些
And that's all I'm gonna say about them.
抱歉  我有顾客来了
Excuse me. I have customers.
肖先生
Mr. Shaw?
你听过把人类DNA融入进性爱机器人的事吗
Have you ever heard of people incorporating human DNA into a sexbot?
那是非法的
That's illegal.
我以为你们知道
And I think you know that.
你可以说你不喜欢机器人
You can say you don't like robots all you want.
你的脉搏却并非如此
Your pulse says otherwise.
什么
What?
准确的说
Precisely.
我想让你黑进肖的客户网络
I want you to hack into Shaw's customer network.
找到那些阿尔巴尼亚人
Find the Albanians.
不需要先拿搜查令吗
We don't need a warrant?
不需要
I agree.
接入网络
搜索阿尔巴尼亚人
找到了
Got it.
五星评价
Five star rating.
有什么计划
What's the plan?
大干一场
Stir the pot.
他们在测试机器人  寻找人类DNA
把手从口袋里拿出来
Hands out of your pockets.
-你见过这个机器人吗  -没有
- You seen this bot? - No.
没见过吗
No?
-见过这个机器人吗  -没有
- Seen that bot? - No, no...
我们测试了所有机器人
We tested all the bots.
全都检查过了  他们没问题
They all check out. They're clean.
好的  谢谢
Okay, thanks.
警官们
Officers.
我是经理  有什么事吗
I'm the manager. Can I help you?
这是你的机器人吗
Is this one of your bots?
不是
No.
我们这里有很多选择
We got a great selection here.
检测到心率升高
我们可以给你找一个和这个非常像的
We can get you pretty close to this one.
我们的机器人通过了所有规定测试
Our bots have passed all the required tests.
警察有优惠
Special rate for cops.
我们最喜欢警察了
We love cops.
-是的  我们最喜欢警察  -很好
- Yeah. We love cops. - Well, great.
如果你能回答我的全部问题
If you answer all of my questions,
也许我能让你们迈出成功的第一步
maybe I'll let you get to first base.
你从塞巴斯蒂安·琼斯和
You ever buy from Sebastian Jones
洛伦佐·肖那里买过机器人吗
and Lorenzo Shaw?
以前买过
We used to.
-不过现在不买了  -为什么不买了
- Not anymore. - Why'd you stop?
我们现在自己做了
We make our own now.
你确定这不是你们做的吗
And you're sure that's not one of them?
说过了
Already said.
约翰
John.
斯塔警探有事和我们说
Detective Stahl needs to talk to us.
谢谢  先生们
Thank you, gentlemen.
他的体征表明他在说谎
His vitals suggest that he is lying.
没错
Yup.
或者是他不怎么喜欢你
Or he doesn't like you very much.
把他列为我们的嫌疑人
Add him to the list of kids and cats.
有银色轿车的线索了
We got a hit for the silver sedan.
那辆在停车场绑走克里斯汀·黑斯曼的车
The one that kidnapped Kristen Haseman in the parking garage.
我们在一个车牌扫描器上发现了它的踪迹
We picked it up on a plate scanner.
多里安  仔细看它经过扫描器的瞬间
Dorian, watch the sedan as it goes past the scanner.
车牌变了
The license plate changes.
他们用了跟踪扰频器
They're using a tag scrambler.
我们一发现这个
Once we realized that,
就直接改用监视摄像头
we switched to straight surveillance cams
并且跟踪它到了第八街的一座工厂
and tracked it to an industrial facility off 8th Street.
他们在那儿做什么
What were they doing there?
不知道  他们停留了20多分钟
I don't know, they were there for 20 minutes,
然后我们跟丢了他们
and then we lost 'em.
好吧  我们三分钟左右后到那里
All right, we're three minutes out.
那是什么
What the hell is that?
是克里斯汀·黑斯曼吗
Is that Kristen Haseman?
这不是人类
It's not human.
识别对象
匹配  不明  性爱机器人
这是宾馆里的那个机器人
This is the android from the hotel.
要是他们就这么处理他们的性爱机器人
If this is what they're doing to their sexbots,
可想而知  他们会如何对待被他们绑架来的女子
imagine what they're doing to the women they've abducted.
迷人的绿色
Beautiful green.
他们把颜色调得刚刚好
They really have got the color just right.
你看  这几枪打得相当精确
You see, these shots were targeted precisely
彻底破坏了皮质继电器和存储中心
to shatter the cortical relays and storage centers.
他们毁坏了她的记忆
They destroyed her memory.
是的  他们要确保没人能恢复她所记录的
Yeah, they wanted to ensure no one could retrieve
关于杀害塞巴斯蒂安·琼斯的凶手的记忆
her recorded memories of Sebastian Jones' murder.
这些白化变种知道他们在做什么
These albinos knew exactly what they were doing.
阿尔巴尼亚人
Albanians.
这样说更合理
Well, that, that would make more sense.
不过还有一丝机会
But there is a small chance that her
她的颞骨外壳可能没被彻底损坏
temporal housing might be intact enough
还能找回一些声象记忆
to salvage some of her echoic memory.
她或许能告诉我们
Uh, she might still be able to tell us
那些人这么做的原因
something about the people that did this.
抱歉  朋友
Apologies, mate.
我习惯一个人单独做这些
I'm used to being alone when I do this.
你们可能不忍直视
You might want to look away.
没关系
It's fine.
他们为什么把它的皮肤剥掉
Why did they peel its skin off?
显而易见  他们也不想让我们看到她的皮
Well, they obviously didn't want us to see that either.
让我想想
Wait a minute,
宾馆里的监控录像里
the surveillance footage at the hotel.
她的手留下的痕迹显示是人类的DNA
Her hands left traces of human DNA.
你觉得他们绑架那些姑娘是为了采集她们的皮肤
You think they're abducting the girls to harvest their skin.
要是用人类皮肤
If you used human skin,
就可以造出市场上最高端的性爱机器人
you'd make the best sex machines on the market.
塞巴斯蒂安查出了这些
I think Sebastian found out about it.
因此他们才杀了他
That's why they killed him.
性爱机器人  约炮机器人
Sex machine, bang bot?
真是目光短浅  不是吗
It's a bit myopic, isn't it?
不是所有找性爱机器人的人都是为了做爱
Not everyone who visits a sexbot is looking for sex.
有些人只是去聊天
Some people go for the conversation
或是结束了一天应付各种有事相求的人
or for a sympathetic ear at the end of a long working day
所带来的疲惫工作之后
surrounded by people who only ever come to visit
去寻求一丝慰藉
when they want something from you.
我是说
I'm just saying that, uh,
神经接口是相当精细的
the neural interface is quite sophisticated.
总之  看上去他们用被绑架的女子的DNA
Anyway, it appears they're growing skin using DNA
来培养皮肤组织
from the abducted women.
合成的皮肤
Well, synthetic skin,
就算再逼真  和真的相比还差很多
as good as it is, is a long way from the real thing.
还要加入能增加吸引力的
There are pheromones and other biological features
信息素以及其他的生物特性
that trigger attraction.
就是这里
Here it is.
抱歉  损坏得太严重了
Sorry, it's too damaged.
如果你们想知道这些机器人从哪里来
If you want to know where these bots are coming from,
我需要研究一个活着的
I'm going to have to get my hands on a live one.
你知道我的意思
So to speak.
你很安静
You're quiet.
发生什么事了
What's wrong?
看着鲁迪工作台上的那个机器人
Just looking at that bot on Rudy's table
不禁让我思考
makes me think,
谁会记得我呢
who is going to remember me?
你是警察
You're a cop.
你帮助过的人们将会永远记得你
The people you help will remember you,
不管你的名字是什么
whatever your name is.
说到名字
Speaking of names,
刚刚有人回复了你的交友档案  约翰
someone just responded to your dating profile, John.
我的交友档...
My dating pro...
-我以为你开玩笑的  -我是认真的
- I thought you were kidding. - Not kidding.
我看到了你盯着性爱机器人的饥渴眼神
I saw the way you were looking at those sexbots.
你的交友名字是...
Your profile name is...
理查德医生
Dr. Richard.
-理查德医生  -喜欢乳蛋饼
- Dr. Richard. - Who likes quiche,
喜欢在沙滩漫步
long walks on the beach,
-和爵士乐  -你居然叫我理查德医生
- smooth jazz. - You seriously did not call me Dr. Richard.
我以为你想找人约会
I thought you wanted to meet someone.
我跟不少女人在约会  不用你帮我
I meet plenty of women. I don't need your help.
我运行了一次身体扫描
I-I ran a bio scan,
看起来你的睾丸已经快饱和了
and it looked like your testicles were at full capacity.
你居然扫描了我的蛋蛋
You're scanning my balls?
-我也不喜欢这样  只是  -老天
- I didn't enjoy it, I just... - Oh, my God,
-真不可思议  -我实在没法不注意到
- This is unbelievable. - I can't help but notice
...你的满腔欲火
you're backed up.
你是有什么毛病
What is the matter with you?
再也不准扫描我的睾丸了
Don't scan my testicles ever again.
收到
Copy that.
她长得什么样子
What does she look like?
你希望她是什么样子
What do you want her to look like?
深邃的褐色眼睛
Brown eyes, soulful.
身高呢
Height?
一般身高就好
Average height.
我喜欢褐发女人
I like brunettes.
你希望跟相同职业的女人约会
Would you date anyone in your profession
还是与你不同职业的
or would you prefer to date someone outside of it?
两种都行
Sure, either way.
我喜欢有智慧的女人  比我更聪明的
I like smart women, you know, women that are smarter than me.
那不是件难事
That won't be hard.
你知道你描述的正是斯塔警探吧
You are aware that you just described Detective Stahl, right?
肯尼思
Kennex.
我们发现你要找的银色轿车了
Hey, we got a 20 on the silver sedan you posted.
我刚将资料传给了多里安
I just uploaded it to Dorian.
好的...  谢谢你...
Uh, okay, thank you, um,
斯塔警探  谢谢
Detective Stahl, thanks.
-好的  谢谢你  斯塔警探  -闭嘴
- Okay, thank you, Detective Stahl. - Shut up.
闭嘴  别闹了
Shut it, zip it.
警察
Police!
不许动
Don't you move!
双手放在仪表盘上
Put your hands on the dashboard! Hands on the dash!
-放在那别动  -不准动
- Hold 'em, keep 'em there! - Do not move!
把你双手放在仪表盘上我能看见的地方
Put your hands on the dashboard now where I can see 'em!
转过身来
Turn around, turn around!
走出车外
Step out of the car.
快点
Come on.
到前面来
Around front.
你好  我是瓦内萨
Hi, I'm Vanessa.
你好吗
Hey, how you doing?
我需要取一份DNA样本
I need to take a DNA sample.
请张开嘴
Open your mouth, please.
为什么
Why?
我已经通过所有测试了
I've passed all my tests.
请
Please.
身份信息  发现匹配
罗琳·怀特
她的DNA属于罗琳·怀特
Her DNA belongs to a Lorraine White,
两个月前在圣克莱尔的一个停车场被绑架
Abducted from a parking structure two months ago in St. Clair.
实验室
Lab.
鲁迪
Rudy,
找了些皮肤给你
found you some skin.
阿尔巴尼亚人不会告诉我们
The Albanians aren't telling us
绑架案受害者在哪里
where the kidnap victims are.
我们得从性爱机器人那里弄到消息
We need to get that information from a sexbot.
现在有三个女孩失踪  也许更多
We have three missing girls out there somewhere, maybe more.
我会尽我所能挖出信息
I'll pull everything I can from it.
又见面了
Hello again.
一个人类的DNA被用来制造你的皮肤
A human's DNA was used to make your skin.
这个女人
This woman.
我们要找到她
We need to find her.
我们时间不多
We don't have much time.
你之前见过她吗
Have you seen her before?
没有
No.
我要你好好想想
I need you to think.
这很重要
It's really important.
那你见过她吗
Have you seen her?
没有
No.
你是在哪里被造出来的
Where were you made?
你的主人是谁
Who owns you?
你知道你在哪里出生的吗
Do you know where you were born?
你跟这个姑娘共事过吗
You ever worked with this girl?
沙琳
Charlene.
没错  沙琳
Right, Charlene.
你知道她在哪里出生的吗
Do you know where she was born?
谁是你的主人
Who owns you?
她可能不太懂这些字眼
She's probably not conscious of those terms.
这些人今晚要带你去哪儿
Where were those men taking you tonight?
他们要带我去兜风
They were taking me for a ride.
我们认为他们要带你去毁掉
We think they were taking you to be destroyed.
为什么会有人想毁掉我
Why would anybody want to destroy me?
跟我可以做远比这更加有趣的事
There are much, much better things to do with me.
如果你不想  我们也可以什么都不做
We don't have to do anything if you don't want to.
我是个很好很好的倾听者
I'm a very, very good listener.
知道吗  人们会用不同的方式寻找联系
You know, people look for connections in different ways.
但所有人都想找的
That's all people are looking for,
其实是一个关心他们的人
is someone who cares about them.
我就是为此而生的
That's what I'm here for.
你知道沙琳在哪儿吗
Do you know where Charlene is?
是的
Yes.
我能见见她吗
Can I see her?
为什么想见她
Why do you want to?
我不知道
I don't know.
你被设计成与人亲近的机器人
You were designed to bond with people.
你被开发出来就是这个目的
That's what you were developed to do.
他们在的时候关注他们
To notice when they're there.
这意味着他们不在的时候你也会关注
That also means you notice when they're not there.
所以你想要见她
That's why you want to see her.
这是你的感觉
That's what you're feeling.
谁让你跟今晚那个男人走的
Who told you to go with the men we found you with tonight?
尤里
Yuri.
你认识尤里吗
Do you know Yuri?
嗯  我们认识尤里
Yeah, we know Yuri.
清空场所
Clear the area.
我负责楼上
I'm going upstairs.
闪开
Move!
该走了
丢弃所有东西
毁掉实验室
他们会死的
他们还能生成很多皮肤
我们会在其他地方建实验室的
我们走
你先上
You go first.
他们不在这
They're not here.
不是这栋楼
This isn't the right building.
办公室也没人
Office is empty, too.
我想我能找到那间皮肤实验室
I think I can find the skin lab.
-鲁迪  -在  多里安
- Rudy? - Yes, Dorian?
这种性爱机器人大部分
Most of these sexbots are platformed
具有老式尤朱诺学习模块
on an old ujuno pendant learning module.
没错  DRN机器人停止使用那些模块以后
Uh, yeah, uh, those modules were available
它们就流入了公共市场
to the public sector once we stopped using them on the DRNs.
停用是因为那些模块会发出
Problem was that they were giving off
多余的GPS信号
an unwanted GPS signal.
对  这是副作用
Yeah, it was an unwanted side effect.
所以每次他们自动更新软件时
Um, whenever they, uh, automatically updated their software,
就会无意中
they'd inadvertently
发出信号从而让相关人员对其追踪
send out a signal allowing those so inclined to, uh, track you.
有这样的记录吗
Is there a log of that?
肯定有
I'm sure there is.
你能读取瓦内萨的内部GPS记录
Can you access Vanessa's internal GPS log
查看模块第一次发出信号是什么时候吗
to find the very first time that the module sent a signal?
应该可以
It's possible.
如果我们能找到她第一次激活的时间
If we can find out the first time she was activated,
-就能找到...-她"出生"的地方
- we can find... - Find out where she was born.
皮肤实验室
The skin lab.
好  稍等一下
All right, bear with me.
很快就好
I won't be a minute.
快看
Oh. Look at that.
这是那个充电器  当我没说
That's the charger for my-- doesn't matter.
找到了
Um, here we go.
就是这个
This is the one I need.
好吧  你好
Right. Uh, hello.
我需要连接你的数据端口
I need to access your data port.
这听起来有点无礼
That sounds rude. Um,
我需要插入我的...天啊  更糟糕了
I need to insert my... Oh, that's even worse.
温柔地
Um... Oh, friendly.
与性爱无关  我保证
Um, it's nothing sexual, I assure you.
我不是说性爱有什么错
Not that there's anything wrong with sex.
我是说  谁不喜欢性呢
I mean, who doesn't like sex?
不是说我
Not me.
我是说我喜欢  这才是重点
I mean, I do. That's-that's the point.
但这就有点
But that would be,
不合时宜了
um, inappropriate at best.
不会疼的  我向你保证
This is not gonna hurt, I promise you.
好了
There we go.
好
Right.
只要...
Just, um...
看看你的...
Having a look at your, uh...
数据记录
statistics.
金士顿高地
看来你第一次被激活的地点是金士顿高地
Looks like you were first activated in Kingston Heights.
安全
Clear!
击毙
Take him out!
不
No!
冲进去
Move it! Move it!
放下武器  把武器放下
Drop that weapon! Drop it, you!
放下武器
Drop the weapon!
别开枪  趴在地上
Don't shoot! On the ground! Now!
安全
Clear!
-安全  -安全
- Clear. - Clear!
安全
Clear!
-这是罗琳·怀特  -她已经死了
- This is Lorraine White. - She's deceased.
打电话给奎斯特  她还活着
Call Bloomquist. She's still alive.
克里斯汀·黑斯曼没死
Kristen Haseman-- she's alive.
维克多见到你肯定会很高兴的
Victor is gonna be very happy to see you.
做得好
Great work.
谢谢
Thanks.
-你该去庆祝一下  -他会的
- You should celebrate. - He will.
你有约会了
You have a date.
说什么
What?
-我没有  -你有
- No, I don't. - Yes, you do--
和约会网站上的佳人有约
With the woman from the dating web site.
什么  不是
Wha...? No.
他的资料很精彩
He has a wonderful profile.
而她很期待与你在七点见面
She's expecting you at 7:00.
那是个
That's a...
只是个玩笑
It's just a... It's a joke, you know.
我有很多女人
I get a lot of women.
也不是很多  只是
I mean, not a lot-- you know, just...
不管怎样  你都该去庆祝
You should celebrate no matter what.
祝你有个美好的  约会夜晚
Have a great night... on your date.
谢谢
Thanks.
晚安
Good night.
机器人班尼迪克又赢了一记
Benedict Android strikes again.
-今晚的约会我不能去  -为什么
- I can't go on a date tonight. - Why?
因为我已经约了我想见的人
Because I've already got someone I want to see.
但约翰  如果你
But, John, if you just...
你写完报告了吗
Do you have your report done?
快写完了
Uh, yeah, almost.
在摧毁机器人时
We'll need individual certificates
我们需要单独的证书 知道吗
when the bots are destroyed. Okay?
知道了
Okay.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我们不能拥有带着人类DNA的机器人
We can't have bots with human DNA.
她不得不停用了
She has to be deactivated.
但是做得好  做得非常好
But well done. Very well done.
-谢谢  -明天见
- Thank you. - See you tomorrow.
你还好吧
You okay?
我想去那里
I'd like to be there.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我要去哪里
Where am I going?
去个更好的地方
To a better place.
你会在那里吗
Will you be there?
我会记得你的
I will remember you.
马蒂
Marty,
你记得约翰·肯尼思吗
do you remember John Kennex?
他曾是你爸爸的搭档
He was your dad's partner.
我想告诉你有关你爸爸的事迹
I want to tell you about your father.
翻译：宝宝  圈圈  Al_ice  胖兔纯
翻译：feilixiaozi  MythCreator  阿阿阿包  Reginamoon
翻译：卫老哥  No.Zero  Silence
时间轴：阿阿阿包  凭陵新月  No.Zero
初校：卫老哥  圈圈
后期：MythCreator  WiLL   总监：紫玉